<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventure on Live before you leave</title>
    <link>https://chasethelist.github.io/tags/adventure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adventure on Live before you leave</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>sample@gmail.com (Dimple Bhuta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>sample@gmail.com (Dimple Bhuta)</webMaster>
    <atom:link href="https://chasethelist.github.io/tags/adventure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Go Scuba Diving</title>
      <link>https://chasethelist.github.io/posts/24_scuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>sample@gmail.com (Dimple Bhuta)</author>
      <guid>https://chasethelist.github.io/posts/24_scuba/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I want to experience the Great Barrier Reef in Australia and here’s what I’ll need:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flights from India to Cairns, Australia: Book a flight to Cairns Airport, the closest major airport to the reef.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Accommodation: Find a comfortable place to stay in Cairns, offering everything from budget hotels to luxury resorts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scuba Diving Packages: Choose from a variety of scuba diving packages, including day trips or liveaboard tours to explore the reef.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Environmental Management Charge (EMC): Be prepared for the AUD 8 fee per person for entering the Great Barrier Reef World Heritage Area.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;PADI Open Water Diver Certification: If I’m not certified yet, I’ll need to take the PADI Open Water Diver course to dive safely in the reef. I’ll explore local diving centers in Mumbai, such as Scuba Diving Mumbai, Bubbles Dive Centre, or S.E.A. Scuba Diving for their courses. The expected price range for the certification is between ₹30,000 to ₹45,000, which generally includes all necessary training, equipment, and certification fees.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hope to achieve this goal before my 50th birthday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embark on a Himalayan Trek</title>
      <link>https://chasethelist.github.io/posts/25_trek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>sample@gmail.com (Dimple Bhuta)</author>
      <guid>https://chasethelist.github.io/posts/25_trek/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post, I will document my journey before, during, and after the Himalaya trek. I am extremely excited to explore the Valley of Flowers, and I have initiated discussions with &lt;a href=&#34;https://indiahikes.com/valley-of-flowers&#34;&gt;India Hikes Company&lt;/a&gt; to facilitate my trek. I wish to achieve this goal by July 25, 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
